hello everybody and welcome to the
大家好，欢迎来到
eighth TV basics tutorial video with
第八节电视基础教程视频带
Python in this video we're going to make
我们即将 制作的 视频中的Python
a sort of drawing application so to do
一种绘图应用程序， 这样做
that from where we are it's actually not
从 我们所处 它实际上不是
very much code because we are already
非常多的代码，因为 我们已经
tracking on touch down on touch and on
触摸 跟踪触摸以及
touch move we actually aren't going to
触摸移动我们实际上不会去
need on touch up but I'm just going to
需要联系，但我只是 要去
leave it here because it's cool that we
把 它留在这里是因为我们很酷
even have that so with that let's go
即使有这样的让我们走吧
ahead and import one more thing and that
提前并导入一件事
is going to be from TV graphics we want
将来自我们想要的电视图像
to import line with a capital L and
导入大写字母L和
that's to actually draw a line basically
这实际上是基本上画出一条线
now what we want to do is on touch down
现在我们想要做的是接触下来
we want to begin a line so think of like
我们想要开始一条线， 所以想想
you know you have a pencil you put the
你知道你有一支铅笔你放
pencil to the paper and it starts to
铅笔在纸上开始
make a mark and then as you drag it
做一个标记，然后拖动它
around it continues you know marking on
围绕它继续你知道标记
the paper so that's what we kind of want
纸所以这就是我们有种想
to do is want touch down if we want to
如果我们想要的话，想做的事情就是想要降下来
begin that mark and then we want to
开始那个标记然后我们想要
continue that mark as long as our touch
只要我们的触摸，继续这个标志
is moving on even though in theory you
即使理论上你也在继续前进
might think in your head well don't we
可能会认为在你的头上 好了，不要我们
have to do something on touch up to stop
必须要做 点事情来阻止
the line drawing no because on touch
这条线不会因为触摸而画
move will just cease to exist anymore so
此举将刚刚停止了 ，所以 存在
we actually don't need to do anything
我们实际上 不需要做 任何事情
there but anyway uh we need line and
但无论如何，我们需要线路和线路
that's really all we have to add as far
这实际上是我们必须增加的一切
as imports are concerned and now we just
因为进口是关心的， 现在我们只是
need to code the on touch down and move
需要编写接下来的代码 并移动
stuff so I'm going to call this uh I
所以我打算把这个叫做我
don't know
不知道
draw clash draw input and then before we
绘制冲突绘制 输入，然后在我们之前
forget we need to take this right here
忘记我们需要把它放在这里
and instead of touch input down here it
而 不是在这里触摸输入
needs to be draw input so I just want to
需要绘制输入，所以我 只是想
change that other than the other mat
改变其他 垫子 以外的其他 垫子
we're ready to go so now we say with
我们现在准备好了 ， 现在我们说出来
self dot canvas and this is the canvas
自我点画布，这是画布
of our application so self dot canvas is
我们的应用程序如此自我点画布
just referring to that so you don't
只是指 那个，所以你没有
really need to like define canvas or
真的需要像定义画布或
anything so with self dot canvas what do
什么都如此自我点画布是什么
we actually want to do well we're going
我们实际上想要做得很好，我们要去
to say touch dot u D and you D now we're
说点触你的D和你D我们现在是
going to reference the line element in
将引用行元素
there and we're going to say that is
那里，我们 要说的是
equal to
等于
line and we're going to say the points
线，我们 要说的要点
over that line is right now going to
在 那一行上现在正在进行
only be a single point in the line but
只有一个点在线，但
the points for now are equal to touch X
现在的点数等于触摸X
touch dot Y so literally the x and y
触摸点Y，从字面上看是x和y
values of where we touch down so line at
我们接触到的位置的值
the moment is literally just actually a
这个时刻实际上只是 一个
point it's not really a line it's simply
点它不是一个 真正 的线，它只是
a point but then what we do is we've
一点，但是我们所做的就是我们
since we've got that now what we're
因为我们现在知道了我们的
going to do is that should I'm going to
要做的是，我应该去
just make sure we close that off right
只要确保 我们 关闭了这一点
yes so now we've got a line there and
是的，现在我们已经有一条线了
that will actually show something but
那实际上会显示一些东西
not very much and now on touch move what
不是很多 ，现在 接触移动什么
we want to do is we're going to say
我们想要做的是我们要说
touch UD and then again we're
触摸UD ，然后再次我们
referencing the line element whoops
引用行元素 哎呀
line like this and then we're going to
像这样的线，然后我们会去
say dot points plus equals and we want
说点加上等于我们想要的
to plus equals the exact same thing
加上等于完全相同的东西
pretty much right here so plus equals
几乎就在这里，所以加上等于
this so again this is just the this is
这个如此反复，这 仅仅 是 这
the line function we're saying we
我们所说的线路功能
already established touch UD line equals
已经建立了触摸UD线等于
line which we imported up here and where
我们在这里和哪里输入的行
we say the points of line so where we
我们说我们的位置在哪里
basically said line dot points because
基本上说线点点是因为
touch UD a line is equal to basically
触摸UD的线等于 基本上
this line right up here so now we're
这条线就在这里，所以现在我们是
saying line dot points which originally
说最初的线点点
line dot points was touch just X&Y of
点线点只是触摸X和Y的
the original touch now we're saying we
现在我们说的是原始的触摸
want to add to those points and we're
想要添加到 这些点，我们是
adding every single movement of touch X
添加触摸 X的每一个动作
and touch y we just add all of those
并触摸y我们 只是添加所有 这些
movements and that's really it that's
运动，那真的就是这样
all we have to do with this and so now
我们现在所需要做的就是这一点
we can just save and run this hopefully
我们可以 保存并有希望地运行
and here we have our application and
在这里我们有我们的应用程序 和
yeah sure enough you can click and you
当然，你可以点击你
can start to write things so hi awesome
可以开始写东西，所以 嗨真棒
and then we can actually you know resize
然后我们可以 真正知道调整大小
this and we'll see that okay we just
这个，我们会看到，没关系，我们只是
gained a lot more space and now we can
获得了 更多的空间，现在我们 可以
write even more stuff and I'm really
写更多的东西，我真的
good at writing with the mouse tutorials
善于 用鼠标教程 写作
you probably won't even know that was
你 可能甚至不知道那是
tutorials immediately
教程立即
anyway so that's that that's pretty much
反正不过就是这样这几乎 是
all of the basics for using canvas
所有 使用 画布 的基础知识
anyways but that's pretty cool like how
无论如何，但如何 非常酷
quickly you can actually you know
很快你 可以真正 知道
reference the drawing ability in the
参考中的绘图能力
canvas ability of TV so anyways I
电视帆布能力，使 反正我
hopefully you guys enjoyed if you have
希望你们喜欢，如果你有
any questions or comments please please
请提出任何问题或意见
feel free to leave them below otherwise
随意将它们留在下面
as always thanks for watching thanks for
一如既往感谢您收看谢谢
all the support subscriptions and until
所有支持订阅和直到
next time
下次